Tinnapat Pongtongmuang

119/12 Latprao 41 Yaek 6-7

Chankasem Chatuchack Bangkok 10900 Mobile: +66991659516

Email: tinnapat@outlook.com



https://www.linkedin.com/in/tinnapat-pongtongmuang-5b0b1377

I earned a Master degree in IT Management.

I've worked in the IT field for over 12 years. I currently work for Kasikorn Bank as a project manager. My major responsibility is to manage projects involving bank prospects and AEC investment by coordinating IT teams with other associated departments in order to achieve business objectives.

Personal details

Date of Birth: Sep 26, 1986 Marital Status: Single Military Status: Exempted

Accomplishments

- Scrum Master Certification
- ITIL 4.0 Foundation
- Effective Negotiation at Work
- Embracing Change Essential
- IT Security Awareness ITIL 4.0
- Foundation Internal Audit for ISO 9001:2008 & ISO 14001:2004
- Microsoft Azure Fundamentals

Expertise

- Project Management
- Business Analysis
- Co-operation
- Negotiation
- SAP (SD, MM), ERPs
- PHP, .Net C#, Java
- SQL
- Web Design

"I hope that my ability and skills would be a person that you are looking for. I believe that your vacancy suited for me to long run and would drive me to be successful on highest level and benefit to your organization."

Work experiences

AVP - Project manager : Dec 2021 - Present

Kasikorn Bank

Manage and implementation projects in AEC to provide sales target to sales team through an analysis of the strengths, weaknesses, and opportunities of the business to reach out target customers and generate the most profitable opportunities.

IT Project manager: Dec 2019 - Nov 2021

Siam Commercial Bank

My responsibility is management for the payment projects. Handling of Credit cards, EDC, QR Payment, ATM and E-wallets.

I supervise the projects that have been assigned by the business units. Working with BA to gathered requirements and communicate with SA and developers to determine suitable plan. I have to interact with Product Owners, Developers, Tester, Network and Security team including to operation team such as Accounting or Support units in order to deliver projects to the business.

Achievement

- E-Wallet partner engagement
- ATM remittance cash-out: Customers can get money from abroad via MoneyGram at the bank's ATM.

IT Operation: Jan 2014 - Dec 2019

SCG Cement-Building materials

I am in charge of IT project management, which includes analysing business challenges and evaluating requirements in order to identify IT solutions. I have led projects by creating project plans, controlling and prioritising project operations, maintaining project financial controls, and providing post-go-live assistance.

Achievement

- VMI : Forecast of dealer's sales volume in order to produce and deliver products.
- S2 Project: ERP system for the company's products and services.
- Roof+: An mobile application used by the company's contractors to track the progress of roof installation.

Web developer: May 2009 - Dec 2013

Bangkok Expressway Plc.

A supervisor, I work as an internal system administrator and also manage the company's website. In my role as a Web developer, I was responsible for determining the best IT solution to fulfill the demands of requesters. I had to do all of the requirements gathering and programming myself. Then involves taking part in system testing with users.

- Expressway's Interactive map (Google map) on www.becl.co.th
- IT Web admin for www.becl.co.th
- Intranet Service Webmasters. (MS SharePoint).

Achievement

- E-Document
- Suggestion system : Web application that welcomes suggestions from company employees. To leave feedback in order to improve the service and working process.

Education

M.Sc. Management Information Systems (GPA 3.45)

King Mongkut's University of Technology North Bangkok

I graduated with a master's degree in MIS.

My Thesis is "The analysis of factors associated with purchasing behavior through online media of Generation Z consumers in Thailand to find the appropriate digital marketing approach."

B.S. Information Technology for Design Field Of Study Information Technology for Design (GPA 3.11) Silpakorn University

I have a bachelor's degree in IT with an emphasis on majority Web an Interactive Media. And some activities during my study in university such as a teacher assistant for the subjects of computer programming, and I was a head of student faculty committee.